(Leonard:)Come on, who's with me?
(Leonard:)Free comic books
to anyone who comes with me.
(Leonard:)I might get punched.
You really want to miss that?
(Raj:)Junior Mints are
pretty apologetic.
(Sheldon:)You're embarrassing
yourself.
(Leonard:)Penny.
(Penny:)What?
Yeah,
(Leonard:)we came to talk to Zack.
Hey, Zack.
(Zack:)What do you want?
(Leonard:)Listen,
(Leonard:)the stuff
we were saying before--
(Leonard:)we were just kidding around.
(Zack:)No, you weren't.
(Zack:)You were making fun
of me.
(Leonard:)Come on, that's what we do.
(Leonard:)We give each other a hard time.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon,
(Leonard:)you look
like a praying mantis.
(Sheldon:)That's very hurtful.
(Leonard:)See?
(Leonard:)I don't know,
it still wasn't very nice.